the VHAT. And then we have the VHAT. And then we have the VHAT. And then we have the
VHAT. And then we have the VHAT. And then we have the VHAT. And then we have the VHAT. And then we have
various secondary endpoints that we've been discussing with the agency. But I don't think
we could provide any further clarity on that one at the moment. Thank you. Thank you. Your next
question comes from the line of Florence Estades from OdoBHF. Please go ahead.
Good afternoon. Thank you very much for taking my question. Florence Estades from OdoBHF.
A quick one for Mukul. Maybe, Mukul, could you give us a little bit more color about one of
the events which impacted the Q2 top line and operating profit margin? Some color on that point
would be great. Thank you. Yeah. Thank you very much, Florence, for the question. So the one-time
phasing that I mentioned, so we have a one percentage point impact on top line. This is
primarily inventory-related changes that we saw across the whole world. This would simply move
from Q2 to Q3. And then we have a one-time phasing that I mentioned. So we have a one-percentage point
of cost that would move to Q3 from an inventory perspective. And then on the cost side, on the R&D
phasing side, we have a couple of clinical trial-related costs that have essentially were
planned for Q2 and now will move to Q3. If you put both of them together, then on the top line,
it's an impact of 1%. And on the bottom line, the accumulated impact of the top line
over-delivery added or compounded by the cost.
phasing leads to a 5% impact on the core operating income.
It's a clear match, very clear. Thanks.
Thank you.
Our next question comes from the line of Colin White from UBS.
Please go ahead.
Hi, Colin White from UBS here.
Thanks for saying my question.
Just to go back to Remy Bruteneb and MS,
please could you recap specifically what gives you confidence
that Remy Bruteneb can improve upon the annualized relapse rate
or about 0.1 that Abagio has achieved in recent RMS studies?
Well, I mean, I think for us, as you know, we don't have phase two data.
So we're basing this based on other BTK inhibitors' performance in similar studies.
You know, we continue to monitor blinded rates for safety and relapse rates.